arwu.org 2012-12-28

# Privacy Policy

ARWU.ORG respects the privacy of its users/visitors and is committed to protect it in all respects. This Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time to incorporate necessary future changes. Changes in this Privacy Policy will become effective when those changes are posted on the site. Please review this statement periodically to ensure that you are happy with any modifications. This Privacy Policy was last updated on 31th October 2010.

### Personal Information Collected by ARWU.ORG

Anyone can view our Web, we automatically gather information about your visits to our Web sites. For accessing the full range of information and services offered across our different sites, a free registration process is required. The ARWU.ORG requires that you provide an email address in order to create an account. You will also be asked for demographic information, this can consist of messages such as your date of birth, nationality, education, occupation, job title, depending on the activity, but it is only collected in aggregate form - no individual user is identified. This is used to manage relationship with visitors and advertisers on our Web sites, to build up marketing profiles and to aid strategic development. 

### Google Analytics and the "Cookies"

The ARWU.ORG uses Google Analytics to recognize you and provide personalization, as well as to help us understand which parts of our Web sites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there, etc. Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze the profile of visitors and provide you with a better user experience.

We reserve the right to place a cookie on your computer with a unique, anonymous number to ensure that your browser does not see the same advertisement repeatedly, to present ads in a series or sequence, and to measure the number of unique visitors who have viewed a particular advertisement. Overall, cookies help us provide you with better service, and customize web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor has provided. A cookie cannot read data off your hard drive. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information that you provide. You may refuse the use of cookies by modifying your browser setting, however, please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. Also we reserve the right to change the vendors who provide us with usage data.

### What We Do With the Information

We require your information to understand your needs so as to customize the Web site and provide you with a better service. We may perform statistical, demographic, and marketing analyses of account holders, to inform advertisers about the nature of our Web traffic. Particularly we may use demographic and preference information to allow advertising on our websites to be targeted, in aggregate, to the users for whom they are most pertinent. This means that users see advertising that is most likely to interest them, and advertisers send their messages to people who are most likely to be receptive, improving both the viewer's experience and the effectiveness of the ads.

### With Whom Do We Share Information

If you have created an account on ARWU.ORG, we will not release or share your email address or any other information that personally identifies you, with any third party including advertisers without your explicit permission. For the sake of using anonymous details about our users to sell appropriate advertising space on the site, we might show an advertiser how many users we have on the site, but it does not mean sharing an individual's details with an advertiser, we only share information about our visitors with the advertiser in aggregate form.

### Links to Other Website

ARWU.ORG contains links to other Web sites for your convenience and information. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question before submitting your personal information.

### Data Security

We will continue to invest in high-quality security and do our utmost to protect users’ privacy, but if you send us email messages, you should be aware that information disclosed in email messages may not be secure or encrypted and thus may be available to others. We suggest that you exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal or confidential information in an email message. We will use your email address to respond directly to your questions or comments.

### Contacting the ARWU.ORG

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or any other aspects of this Web site, please contact us via email at [contact@shanghairanking.com](mailto:contact@shanghairanking.com).
